{
    "subject": "resource/Prince_of_Persia:_The_Sands_of_Time",
    "predicate": "property/programmer",
    "object": "Claude Langlais",
    "human_readable": "The programmer of Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time is Claude Langlais.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9592236876487732,
            "question": "Who programmed Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8962653279304504,
            "question": "Besides Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time, what other games has Claude Langlais worked on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7779518961906433,
            "question": "What is the name of the game Claude Langlais programmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.637601912021637,
            "question": "Is Claude Langlais a game developer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5684379935264587,
            "question": "What game did Claude Langlais program?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5415544509887695,
            "question": "What year was Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.45907893776893616,
            "question": "What is Claude Langlais's role in game development?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44485360383987427,
            "question": "What type of games is Claude Langlais known for developing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32939934730529785,
            "question": "Does Claude Langlais have any other notable works in the gaming industry?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2625364661216736,
            "question": "Name a video game created by Claude Langlais."
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The programmer of Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time is Claude Langlais.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1949_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does Claude Langlais have any other notable works in the gaming industry?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1949_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of games is Claude Langlais known for developing?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1949_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Claude Langlais's role in game development?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1949_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_9.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_92.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1949_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents states that Claude Langlais worked on \"Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time\" as a programmer. Therefore, the statement \"The programmer of Prince of Persia: The Sands of Time is Claude Langlais\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}